David/PER William/PER Donald/PER Cameron/PER (born 9 October 1966) is a British politician who has served as the Prime Minister of the United/ORG Kingdom/ORG since 2010, as Leader of the Conservative/ORG Party/ORG since 2005 and as the Member of Parliament for Witney/ORG since 2001 . Cameron/PER studied  Philosophy, Politics  and  Economics  at  Brasenose/ORG Col-lege/ORG, Oxford/ORG . He then joined the Conservative/ORG Research/ORG Department/ORG and became spe-cial adviser, first to Norman/PER Lamont/PER and then to Michael/PER Howard/PER . He was Director of Corporate Affairs at Carlton/ORG Communications/ORGfor seven years . Cameron/PER first stood for Parliament in Stafford in 1997 .
